♪ 'Twas brillig, and the slithy toves ♪
♪ Did gyre and gimble in the wabe; ♪
♪ All mimsy were the borogoves, ♪
♪ And the mome raths outgrabe. ♪
♪ "Beware the Jabberwock, my son! ♪
♪ The jaws that bite, the claws that catch! ♪
♪ Beware the Jubjub bird, and shun ♪
♪ The frumious Bandersnatch!" ♪
♪ He took his vorpal sword in hand: ♪
♪ Long time the manxome foe he sought— ♪
♪ So rested he by the Tumtum tree, ♪
♪ And stood awhile in thought. ♪
♪ And as in uffish thought he stood, ♪
♪ The Jabberwock, with eyes of flame, ♪
♪ Came whiffling through the tulgey wood, ♪
♪ And burbled as it came! ♪
♪ One, two! One, two! And through and through ♪
♪ The vorpal blade went snicker-snack! ♪
♪ He left it dead, and with its head ♪
♪ He went galumphing back. ♪
♪ Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle... ♪
♪ The Queen of Hearts, she made some tarts, ♪
♪ All on a summer day; ♪
♪ The Knave of Hearts, he stole those tarts, ♪
♪ And took them clean away! ♪
♪ Will you walk a little faster? ♪
♪ Said a whiting to a snail. ♪
♪ There's a porpoise close behind us, ♪
♪ And he's treading on my tail. ♪
♪ See how eagerly the lobsters ♪
♪ And the turtles all advance! ♪
♪ They are waiting on the shingle— ♪
♪ Will you come and join the dance? ♪
♪ Will you, won't you, will you, ♪
♪ Won't you, will you join the dance? ♪
♪ Won't you, won't you join the dance? ♪